found.info 2016-04-14

# Privacy Policy | found.info

**1\. Found.info are committed to protecting your personal information and other data provided to us.**  
This Privacy Policy explains how we use your personal information, including setting out the circumstances where we might provide it to third parties.

**2\. What information do we collect and what do we do with it?**  
2.1 To take advantage of some of our services you will be required to log on or register with the Web Site. We may use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server and to administer our Web Site. The information will be collected when you register with the Web Site in order to use any of the services available via the Web Site.  
2.2 We may use the information that we collect to personalise your experience on the Web Site, to help you log on in future and to continue to use the Web Site, and to help us select services or materials for inclusion on the Web Site that may be of interest to you. We may need to pass your information to third parties who help us to maintain, administer or develop this Web Site but, if so, that information is only given to those third parties for that limited purpose – we DO NOT give your information to any third party mailing list services.  
2.3 We also monitor traffic patterns and usage of our Web Site to help us improve our Web Site design and layout. We may pass this information to our partners or other third parties but it will NOT contain any personally identifying information.  
2.4 Found.info may want to contact you to notify you of news about us, changes to the Web Site, special events or new services or products that we think may interest you. You can opt out or in to these services at any time.  
2.5 Found.info reserves the right to access and disclose personal data or information to comply with applicable laws and lawful government requests, to operate its systems properly, or to protect itself or its users.

**3\. Sharing of Information with Third Parties**  
3.1 We follow security procedures as required by the UK Data Protection Act 1998, in the storage and disclosure of personal information that you have given us, to prevent unauthorised access to such information. At times we may let you know about the products or services provided by carefully selected third parties. Found.info DO NOT give your information to any third party mailing list services.

**4\. Your Consent**  
4.1 You acknowledge and agree that, in the course of using this Web Site or registering with it and any services offered via this Web Site, certain information about you will be captured electronically or otherwise and transmitted to Found.info or to third parties who host our web servers or assist us in maintaining this Web Site; and  
4.1.2. Found.info may send your information outside of the European Economic Area for processing or use in accordance with this Privacy Policy.  
4.2 If ordered by a court of competent jurisdiction to provide any of your personal information collected by Found.info as described in this Privacy Policy, you consent to Found.info providing such personal information to that court in accordance with the court’s instructions.  
4.3 By using this Web Site, you expressly agree to the collection and use of your information as set out above for the purposes set out in this Privacy Policy.

**5\. Our Responsibilities – How does Found.info protect user information?**  
5.1 We seek to limit our employees’ access to your information about you to those employees who need to have such information to service your account. We emphasise to our employees the confidential nature of user information and the high level of importance that Found.info places on maintaining this confidentiality.

**6\. Changes to Privacy Policy**  
We reserve the right to add to or change the terms of this Privacy Policy in our sole discretion, without prior notice to you. If we change this Privacy Policy, we will post the new Privacy Policy on the Web Site, and it will become effective from the time of posting to the Web Site. Please visit this Privacy Policy on a regular basis to make sure you have read the latest version and you understand what we do with your information.
